A magical journey to a place where the past and present meet
Little Buddha is a drama, history film directed by Bernardo Bertolucci.
After the death of Lama Dorje, Tibetan Buddhist monks find three children — one
American and two Nepalese — who may be the rebirth of their great teacher.
Siddhartha, played by Keanu Reeves.
Lisa Conrad, played by Bridget Fonda.
Dean Conrad, played by Chris Isaak.
Lama Norbu, played by Ruocheng Ying.
Jesse Conrad, played by Alex Wiesendanger.
Raju, played by Raju Lal.
Little Buddha is a 1993 drama film directed by Bernardo Bertolucci, written by Rudy Wurlitzer
and Mark Peploe, and produced by usual Bertolucci collaborator Jeremy Thomas.
An international co-production of Italy, France and the United Kingdom, the film stars Chris Isaak,
Bridget Fonda and Keanu Reeves as Prince Siddhartha (the Buddha before his enlightenment).
The film explores themes of buddhist, tibet, reincarnation, buddha, siddhartha.
The tone is emotional.